Hi, Luisa!
I know you said before
that he's quite a loser.
I'm talking about Angelito.
He invited me to go somewhere.
Concert… Do you wanna come?
I'll bring my boyfriend.
Double date.
She's just a police agent
hovering around Mikoy.
After Carlota kills this agent,
I will show her head to Mikoy.
Why are you yelling?
Alex still hasn't arrived
for our morning briefing.
Sianong, check her apartment.
Bok?
Bok!
Hello, cutie.
- Where's Alex?
- What are you doing here?
Bok, you weren't at the briefing.
You weren't answering my calls.
Of course, I'd be worried.
What is this?
You kidnapped her?
She attacked me last night.
Okay.
We need to bring her to HQ.
We interrogate her, by the book.
I know that.
Bok.
Then don't be here.
Get out.
- No.
- So you have deniability.
No.
You don't do this!
You're not like this.
What's going on with you?
Why is it different with this mission?
Huh?
Someone has to do it, Bok.
- No.
- Get out.
You don't break--
Bok, come on!
Bok!
Hello, sir?
Agent Sianong, how's Agent Alex?
She's okay, sir. She just overslept.
She's a bit under the weather, sir.
I'll stay here for now, sir.
Just to make sure she's really okay.
All right, Agent Sianong, stay with her.
Tell her she doesn't need
to report in today.
Yes, sir. Copy that.
Do your worst.
I know people like you by heart.
But you should know better.
Because if not,
let me just tell you…
I've subscribed
to the Miley Cyrus principle.
I need to know why Alex came to see me.
I need to talk to her.
There.
Dial it, Mikoy.
So we can finally find out your secret.
Ring, ring.
Mikoy.
Let's go.
From now on, the phone we gave you…
Don't use it anymore.
We've got you covered. We'll contact you.
We'll find a way.
I'll get you at the right time.
Double date.
With Angelito and Luisa Mae.
Really, Sofie?
Oh, come on!
You know, Sofie,
you're smart.
But you know what you did?
That wasn't smart at all.
All you say is yes
and rushing in.
And now what?
Nothing!
Oh, Sofie…
Hi, sir.
Instead of just standing there,
why don't you join me?
Just pretend to be my boyfriend.
You know, this is just one time.
You don't need to talk.
I'll handle the whole love story.
Where we met, where we dated.
And I'll even explain your personality.
You're the quiet type.
I'm the extrovert.
That's why we're a perfect match.
Deal?
Come on, just agree
to have a date with me.
- Sofie.
- You'll be my date.
What are you doing?
You're even involving the standee.
Stop. Freeze.
I said freeze!
VERTEX
GLOBAL
I've been calling her for a while now,
but she's not answering.
And she hasn't ended up
in a dangerous situation.
Why?
Who are you?
You're talking too much.
Just put your hands up.
Alex, what are you saying?
I said let her go.
Release her now.
And that's an order, Agent Sianong.
Bye, cutie.
Compared to men, right?
Women really are at a disadvantage.
Try this.
A bit weird, but it's good.
- It is good!
- I told you.
By the way, sir.
Chiara mentioned
that Carlota is your chihuahua.
Why would she say that?
My daughter…
She has a way with words, you know.
Sometimes…
her imagination goes too far.
Is Carlota here because
you want someone to watch over me?
Why, sir?
Am I doing anything here at Vertex
that you don't approve of?
Is that why you're having me watched?
What are you thinking, dear?
It's Mikoy.
Something is still off.
The other night, he woke up screaming,
drenched in sweat,
but he wouldn't talk to me about it.
He was so dismissive.
He said it was just a dream.
I can clearly see it's affecting him.
I'm worried, Mama.
That's just how men are.
They say, "I'm fine,"
even when they're not.
Dear, I think
there's something worse
you should be worried about.
Not his nightmares.
Not even his silence.
Your father found out
that there are agents following Mikoy.
So I think I can handle
anything, Uncle Vik.
Like what, Uncle Vik?
Is there something I should know?
So…
he's investigating our family
through Mikoy.
Are you sure?
Well…
You know your father.
He has so many theories.
Of course, he overthinks.
But you know our situation, dear.
It pays to overthink.
And of course,
it's your father's responsibility
to worry about us.
So…
we need to keep an eye on Mikoy.
Better yet, dear…
Maybe it's time to tell him the truth.
Why did you let her go?
But what did you do?
That's dereliction of duty!
You let La Fornarina go.
- She is not La Fornarina.
- Fine.
Then how?
La Fornarina is left-handed.
What are you doing?
Freeing you.
You're no use to me.
I have the weapon.
You're at a disadvantage.
Why don't you try?
I told you we're not on the same level.
If you let me walk out of here,
I'll come back for you,
and I'll make sure I kill you.
What's so funny?
What do you think he'll do to you?
He might even suspect
that you're working with us
because I let you go.
So I will give you an option.
Work with me, and I'll
protect you from Viktor.
I can handle my own battles.
That's your decision.
Up to you.
You're playing
a very dangerous game, Alex.
Sometimes, we need
to think outside the box.
Why did you even say that?
You don't even have a boyfriend.
Ouch.
Did you really have
to announce I'm single?
Okay, that's not what I meant.
Sorry.
Let's do this instead.
I'll be your date.
Yes.
Are you serious?
You're volunteering?
I'm serious, for real.
Limited time only.
If I were you, I'd take the offer, Sofie.
And honestly, it'd be sad
if you showed up without a date
for the double date you agreed to.
Fair point.
But let me ask you something.
Why are you volunteering
to be my boyfriend?
Fake boyfriend.
Okay, fine, fake boyfriend.
But still.
Why are you really doing this?
What is it? Do you have
too much free time?
Are you bored?
Oh, I know this type.
You like me, don't you?
You secretly like me,
and you're hoping that one day
I'll notice you.
Oh, wow. Your style is terrible.
You're really annoying, you know that?
Simple. If you don't want to, then don't.
Hey, Laurence. Just kidding.
Come on.
Sorry.
It's just a joke.
Don't be so sensitive.
Come on. Let's make up.
Do you want to know
why I volunteered to be your date?
Huh? But why?
Because I like you.
Your face looks like
you just won the lottery.
Hey. Don't tell me you're sulking.
Sulking!
Why are you still alive?
I escaped, sir.
But I'm injured.
Marie.
Is this the complete manpower list
of our drivers?
Yes, sir. That's what I already
gave Ma'am Carlota.
That's what she requested.
But…
It feels like something's missing.
Can I see, sir?
Oh.
Yes, it seems so, sir.
Maybe it got missed in the photocopy, sir.
Right away, sir.
Morning, sir.
Someone is waiting for you.
Here, sir. It's complete now.
Hmm…
This one.
Jose Cuenca.
Late. Late again.
Late once more.
Over and over again.
These drivers are always delayed
with deliveries.
But it feels like…
like nothing happens.
There is no sign of reprimand.
Sir, I don't know.
Okay, you can go.
Okay, sir.
I need to report this to Agent Alex.
Gotta make that call, buddy.
Let's go.
There it is.
Keep it going.
I need to know your secrets.
Norberto.
What's the agent's name?
But Mikoy, what are you even doing here?
Come here.
I just missed you.
Do you feel the same way about me?
You really love leading people on, Mikoy.
Such a heartbreaker.